Here I am Russell Brand with doctor
professor doctor doctor professor true
of him Pearson you've got to join us and
watch and listen to under the skin what
did we talk about
Oh God it was everything under the Sun
yeah yeah you're you're an exhausting
interviewer in the best possible we
really really enjoyed it I think it was
a good open conversation I think we we
went through a lot of topics such as we
talked about their controversies that
you've been involved with some of even
some of my controversies if you enjoy it
the world ought to body inequality
politics power the government means what
words mean where power lies I mean it's
pretty good cause we both have got vague
headache yes yes both little bit sort of
exhausted this will really be the bit
where we would say something stupid so
please listen to under the skin and what
do you like your life really you could
you could do that into that within the
scope of your freedom right right
thank you thank you thank you very much
fun yeah